《越狱》前情回顾
Previously on Prison Break
我和你有个很大不同 迈克尔
there's one big difference between you and I, Michael.
你不会杀人
You can't kill.
我会逮到你
I will get you.
这个 呃... 万一你遇到麻烦
This is, uh...in case you run into trouble down the road.
沿着这路走
down the road.
林肯 你父亲真的很想见见你弟弟和你
Lincoln, he really wants to see you and your brother.
他在你弟弟十岁后就没见过他
He hasn't seen Michael since he was ten years old.
我们走
Let's go!
迈克尔从未见过你爷爷
Miael never met your grandfather.
爸爸
Dad.
-我找到布伦斯了-干掉他们
I got Burrows.Take care of them.
我想我有点享受这件事
I think there's a part of me that enjoys this.
感觉好像在追吸毒一样的快感
It feels to me like chasing a high.
现在我更了解状况了
And I should know better by now.
莎拉?
Sara?
嗨 莎拉
Hi,Sara
嘿 这是什么?
Hey, what is this?
这是... 量血压的
It's for my... blood pressure.
-盖瑞 我们可以做笔交易 好吗?-不行
-Geary, come on, we can make a deal, man.-No deals.
你最后的筹码都用完了 伙计
You just crapped out your last bargaining chip, pal.
这难道不是你所见过最美的东西吗?
Ain't that the most beautiful thing you ever seen?
我们是警察
This is the Tribune Police.
请马上出来
Make yourself known.
你真走运
Hey, you're in luck.
在后面有一盒
Had a case in back.
很好
Excellent.
鱼杆滑轮润滑油
Fishing reel oil.
你整盒都要?
And you want the whole case?
整盒
Whole case.
还有 GPS定位器?
And the, uh, GPS?
是的 GPS定位器
And the GPS.
一定是有很多鱼要钓了?
Must do quite a bit of fishing.
是啊 很多鱼...
Yeah, a lot of fishing...
并不是所有的都要抓到
not a whole lot of catching.
96美圆23美分
$96.23.
我只买滑轮润滑油吧
Um...I'm just going to take the reel oil.
谢谢
Thank you
你得付钱
Hey!You have to pay for that.
拿走吧 请不要伤害我
Just take it; please don't hurt me.
求你了
Please.
你要付出代价的
You have to pay for that.
打开抽屉
vault.Open it.
为了大家
One for the team.
他不是在追捕我 而是我女儿
He wasn't gunning for me,he was gunning for my daughter.
告诉安娜我爱她
Give Anna her papa's love.
我会把你的喉咙给割断
I'm going cut your throat out.
我爱过你 迈克尔
I loved you, Michael.
你却利用了我
You just used me.
警察发现了你女友
Cops found your girlfriend fish-belly white,
脸色惨白  口吐白沫
gargling her own puke.
反正你不会关心
And what do you care?
只要她把那门开着就得了
As long as she left the door open.
能遇上你我感到很幸运
I feel very fortunate to have met you.
对不起 亨利
I'm sorry, Henry.
掌握政府是为了公司的利益
It's about corporate interests taking over the government--
买到选票 打仗
buying elections, fighting wars...
有人会死 他们从而得利
people dying so they can turn a profit.
我们想要阻止这些
We're trying to stop it.
那你们是什么 一大堆间谍?
What are you, a bunch of spies?
仅仅是一些议员和国会里的人
Just a handful of senators, congressmen,
以及像我那样曾经为公司出过力的人
people like me that once worked for the company.
人们想要揭露总统
People willing to expose
揭开他的本来面目--
the president for what she is--
一个公司抛出去的诱饵
a shill working for these corporations.
我们要拉她下台
We bring her down,
要击垮他们
we bring them down.
这和我有什么关系?
What's it got to do with me?
因为我们拉她下台的办法就是让你获得自由的办法
Because the way we're going to bring her down is also what we're going to use to set you free.
大约一礼拜前 我们终于取得了突破
About a week ago, we finally got a break.
一位国家安全局的分析师同意了我们的计划
An nsa analyst sympathetic
他最终想办法进入并弄明白了那个梯次程序
to our cause finally worked his way up and got clearance into the Echelon program.
全国各地的电子邮件以及电话
E-mails, cell phone calls all across this country,
只要被传送 就会通过那个梯次程序
if it's transmitted, it goes through Echelon.
会被分类 翻译 并且储存下来
It's calogued, interpreted,and then stored
为了国家的安全
for homeland security.
他们什么都不会放过
Nothing is missed by them.
任何一切
Nothing.
包括 一次偶然的机会
Including, by accident,
在9-11后几个月...
for a few months after 9-11...
白宫
the white house.
那分析师监听到了总统和特伦斯·斯蒂德曼的电话
The analyst got his hands on a phone conversation the president had with Terrence Steadman...
两周以后
two weeks after
就会安排你杀了他
you supposedly killed him.
后来 那分析师想要把这情报带出来
Now, the analyst tried to get this information out of the building...
...但后来发现有其他人也在监听
but it turns out, someone else was snooping, too.
(想知道真相就打开)
If you really want to know
某些其他人 想要知道总统的一些事
Someone else wanted answers about the president.
艾尔多和林肯想要单独待着
Aldo and Lincoln want to be left alone.
当然了 我明白
Sure, I understand.
24小时后 唐克雷蒂州长死了
24 hours later, tancredi is dead,
那分析师也失踪了
the analyst is missing,
而且白宫的梯次程序录音带也从主机上被删了
and the white house Echelon tapes have been deleted from the mainframe.
那卷录音应该还在
The tape is still out there.
想想他们对唐克雷蒂·莎拉追的那么紧
And judging by how hard they're going after Sara tancredi,
我很肯定他们认为录音带就在她那
I'm pretty sure they think she has it.
而且我想他们是对的
And I think they're right.
她是整件事的关键
She's the key to this whole thing,
林肯
Lincoln.
LJ  跟我来
LJ, COME WITH ME.
我知道你现在觉得被背叛了
I would imagine that you're feeling slightly betrayed right now.
我明白
I understand.
你也该知道了
As you can see,
我不叫兰斯 也不是个吸毒者
hi, my name is not lance,and I'm not an addict.
好吧
okay.
现在我有件事对你来说很重要
There is one thing about me that should mean a great deal to you right now.
那就是我是一个通情达理的人
That is I am reasonable.
只要你告诉我你所知道的 我就放你走
If you tell me what you know, you get to go.
好吧 或许
Okay, and then maybe
考虑到我们之间的关系
when this is all behind us,
你应该想一想我们以前的老交情
we get to grab a piece of pie for old times' sake.
好吗
Okay.
我不知道迈克尔在哪
I don't know where Michael is.
这和迈克尔无关 是关于你父亲的
This is not about Michael; this is about your father.
他在华盛顿留了些东西
He left washington with
一些不属于他的东西
something that didn't belong to him.
我们想要回来
We need it back.
就为了这你杀了他?
And you killed him for it.
不 我没有 这不值得我这么做
I didn't, no, for what that's worth.
但我也希望他的死
But I hope that his death
让你清楚地明白了现在的状况
properly illustrates the magnitude of the situation that we're in right now.
东西在哪?
Sowhere is it?
我不知道你说什么
I don't know what you're talking about.
在哪?
Where is it?
我不知道你在说什么
I don't know what you're talking about.
在哪?
Where is it?
我不知道你在说什么
I don't know what you're talking about.
莎拉 对这事我还有进一步的办法
Sara, there's a next step involved in this,
你一定不会想尝尝的
and you don't want to experience that.
我向天发誓 我真的不知道你说什么
I swear to god I don't know what you're talking about.
我爸爸没给我任何东西
My father didn't give me anything.
我真的不知道你在说什么
I don't know what you're talking about.
保佑我神父  我有罪
bless me, father, for I have sinned.
你上一次忏悔是什么时候?
How long has it been since your last confession?
这是第一次
This is my first time.
有生以来
In a long time.
你知道你的罪行的本质吗?
Are you aware of the nature of your sins?
本质?
The nature?
我不太确定
I'm not really sure.
在你内心深处你是知道的
Deep down inside your heart, you know.
也许是正义的吧
Righteousness, maybe.
相信到最后能为我的所做所为正名
Believing the ends justify the means.
你的最后目的是什么？
What are those ends?
拯救一个人的生命
Saving someone's life.
那你的所做所为呢?
And the means?
我几乎破坏了所有的法律
I've broken just about every law you can name.
但这不仅仅是我所做过的事...
But it's not just what I've done.
还有其他人做的事...
It's what others have done...
...因为是我让他们做的
because I let them.
因为我觉得自己在做正确的事
Because I was doing what I thought was right.
本来这次我应该更明白的...
I should have known better this time.
这次?
This time?
当我还是个孩子的时候...
When I was a kid...
我眼看着一个人流血致死
I watched a man bleed out and die.
而且我很高兴...
And I was glad...
因为这是他应得的
because he deserved it.
生命
Life
-是只有上帝才有权赋予或者带走的  孩子-突然间
is only for god to give and take, my son.-Suddenly,
在我内心就有了阴影
there is this dark space inside of me.
我知道那是不对的
And I knew it was wrong.
但事已至此
But here I am.
有办法来挽回的
There is a way to stop this.
把你的意志交给上帝
Surrender your will to god.
如果我现在放弃
If I surrender now,
我会失去我所爱的一切
I lose everything that I love.
会失去你的灵魂吗?
But do you lose your soul in the process?
人人都有自己的信仰
Well, we all have our crosses to bear.
你还好吗?
You okay?
这永远都不会停止
This is never gonna stop.
他们会不断来追杀我们
They're gna keep coming after us.
林肯  别接
Lincoln, don'T.
搞定了吗?
Is it done?
你完了
You are.
林肯 布伦斯
Lincoln Burrows.
你的人死了
Your man's dead.
和你派来杀我儿子的其他人一个下场
Just like anyone else you send to take out my son.
我们要的是你
We want you.
和LJ没关系
This isn't about LJ.
有个很简单的办法
There's a very simple way
让这一切都结束
for all of this to end.
我来告诉你这会怎么结束--
I'll tell you how it's going to end--
我会亲手掐死你
me staring in your dead eye with my hand around your throat.
你都不知道我是谁
You don't even know who I am.
还有多远?
How much further?
17号国道 墨西哥边境以北75英里处
COUNTY ROAD 17  75 MILES NORTH OF THE MEXICAN BORDER
就这里吧
Right here is good.Alright you got it.
谢了
Thanks for the ride.
小意思
No problem.
马宏探员
Agent Mahone.
我是比尔 金
Bill Kim.
是来接你的
I'm here to pick you up.
我叫的是克里曼
I called Kellerman.
他现在忙着呢
He's busy right now.
有别人知道你在这里吗?
Does anyone else know you're here?
-没有-那就好
-No.-Good.
你能把门打开吗?
Can you open the gate?
我还需要辆车
And I need a new vehicle.
我想你还不够了解我
There's something you should know about me.
我不太喜欢直接参与到行动中
I don't like being out in the field.
只有出了茬子我才会来
I only do so when there's been a screwup.
我现在也参与了  亚历山大
I'm out in the field, Alex.
那么你为什么不把门打开?
Then why don't you open the gate?
然后就赶快回华盛顿去
You can hurry back to D.C.
免得把鞋弄脏了
before your shoes get dirty.
我们有个线索可以知道林肯
We have a lead as to where Burrows
和他弟弟碰头的地点
will be meeting up with his brother.
一个他叫波茨瓦波什的地方
It's a place he referred to as "Bolshoi Booze."
你知道那个地方吗?
Does that mean anything to you?
是的  那是斯科菲尔德身上的一百多个纹身之一
Yeah, it's one of a hundred tattoos on Scofield's body.
是什么意思?
What does it mean?
我现在还不知道
I don't know yet.
你必须要在接下来的
You'll need to figure it out
几个小时里面破解出来
within the next couple of hours.
如果斯科菲尔德和布伦斯越过了边境
If Scofield and Burrows cross the border,
他们就在你的司法权之外了
they'll be out of your jurisdiction,
你对我们也就没价值了
and you'll be of no further value to us.
开门
Open the gate.
然后你能做什么?
So you can do what?
我想先听听
I want to hear it.
这位本来指望着帮我们结案的人打算怎么做
Straight from the mouth of the guy who's supposed to be our closer.
我会抓住斯科菲尔德
I'll get Scofield
和布伦斯...还有剩下的人
and Burrows...and all of the rest of them.
之后你和我
And then me and you
还有凯勒曼
and Kellerman,
各走各的路
we're going to part ways.
我只希望你动机明确
I just hope you're properly motivated.
因为只要你尽职了 我们就不会记起查尔斯的事
'Cause as long as you do your job, we'll forget about Shales.
然后你就能回科罗拉多去见你的儿子
And then you can go back to Colorado and visit your son.
卡麦隆
Cameron.
他五岁了  是吧?
He's five, right?
不许你再提起他的名字
Don't you ever mention his name again.
这就对了
There he is.
这就是我想听的
That's what I wanted to hear.
去破解它  亚历山大
Get cracking, Alex.
好多人就指望着你了
A lot of people are relying on you.
珍妮会照顾好的  你可以信任她
Jane will take care of it; you can trust her.
我知道这很不容易
I know this is hard,
但是会好起来的  相信我
but it will work out--you have my word.
-谢谢-多加小心
-Thank you.-Be careful.
听着  恩...
Listen, uh...
我明白
I know.
珍妮会照顾你的
Jane's gonna look after you.
我都不认识她
I don't even know her.
她没问题的
She's all right.
她为爸爸做事已经有段时间了
She's been working for Dad for a while.
我会...
I'll, uh...
我很快就会见到你的  我保证...
I'll see you soon, I promise.
是不是你爸爸也这么跟你说过?
Isn't that the same thing your dad told you?
是的  但我说话算话
Yeah, but I mean it.
是我
Hey.Hey, it's me.
收到给我打个电话好吗?
Just call me when you get this, okay?
有要紧事
It's important.
这是数字
the numbers...
这个是我的报酬吗？
Is that my payment?
医用硝化甘油
Medical nitroglycerine?
我答应过你的
As promised.
你可不了解要弄到这样的货色有多难
You have no idea how hard it is to get this kind of grade.
就算利用我的关系也未必可以
Even with my contacts.
那么该是你实现交易的时候了
It's time for your end of the deal.
飞机在哪里？
Where's that plane gonna be?
降落前几小时他们会打电话告诉我地点的
They call me a couple of hours before with the drop-off point.
为了甩掉药品管理局的追踪
It keeps the DEA off our backs.
既然还有一会时间
Since it's going to be a while,
进去避避太阳吧
you might want to stay out of the sun.
(西班牙语)
有问题吗？
Is there a problem?
他们是我的表兄弟
They're my cousins.
在你父亲得到消息之前
Now, after your father accessed
他用手机打了3个电话
this information, he made three calls from his cell phone,
全都是给你的
all to you.
他告诉了你什么？
What did he tell you?
他刚从芝加哥回来
Just that he was coming back to Chicago.
好
Good.
你现在变老实了 很好
You're being honest. Good.
在你父亲飞机降落和你到家的时候
Now, there's a half an hour between when your father landed
有半个小时的间隔 我不清楚
and when he got home that is unaccounted for.
我知道你曾在他办公室停留过
I know you stopped by his office.
-你见到了他吗？-没有
-Did you see him there?-No.
我最后次见他是在书房 但是已经死了
The last time I saw my father,he was dead in his study.
他让其他人给你任何消息了吗?
Did your father have anyone give you anything?
你认为我会隐瞒你什么吗？
Do you think that I'm just withholding information
因为我喜欢和你在一起
because I like hanging out with you?
所以如果我知道什么事情
If I knew something,
我会告诉你的  但是我不知道
I would tell you; I don't.
我对此一无所知
I don't know anything about any of this.
真的?
Really?
那么为什么你会给他
Then why did you give your father the file
关于林肯布伦斯的资料
on Lincoln Burrows?
为什么你会为斯科菲尔德开门
Why did you open the door for Scofield,
帮他逃出监狱
and help him escape?
为什么他寄给你这些密笺?
Why did Scofield send you those coded notes?
为什么你会来新墨西哥见他?
Why did you come to New Mexico to meet him?
别和我耍花样
Don't try to float a babe-in-the-woods routine by me.
你这样会让我很生气 那么...
It's really going to piss me off, so...
说吧
Come on.
没事的
You're okay.
听着 莎拉
Look, Sara.
你知道  我们正在达成共识  对吧
We're going to have to come to an understanding.
是的 你是对的 他们是预谋好的
Yeah, you were right;they are coordinates.
在GPS上定好他们的坐标
Plug them into your GPS.
他们会带你去一个地方
They'll take you to a spot in the New Mexico desert.
大概在沙漠的某个中心
It's in the middle of nowhere, basically.
谢谢
Thanks.
好的 没问题
Yeah, no problem.
长官  你在和谁见面?
Sir, who are you meeting?
他究竟在干什么?
What the hell is he doing?
让我们别插手  他就在干这个
He's keeping us out of the loop,that's what he's doing.
多次逃过了法律的制裁
Constantly running from the law with a bad heart...
墨西哥  我的故乡 有许多好东西
Mexico, where I'm from has got a lot of great things,
但是...没有好的医疗条件
but... health care ain't one of them.
你还好吧?
You all right?
你有点紧张
You look a little nervous.
我可不是天天都干这个的
I don't do this every day.
我想知道关于这架飞机
I just want to get the information on that plane
还有
and, uh...
继续上路
move on.
就这样？
Is that it?
就这样
我知道你是谁
I know who you are.
你看上去有点紧张
You don't have to worry
我们不会和联邦探员有交易
we can't go within 100 feet of a federal marshal
去领奖赏的
to collect the reward,
因为我们的脑袋在美国和墨西哥都没有保障
'cause we got U.S. and Mexican warrants on our heads.
但是至于去巴拿马的飞机
But this plane to Panama...
坐下吧
Sit down.
这全都是为了你的哥哥?
This is all for your brother?
是的
Yes.
我有4个兄弟 2个在监狱
I got four brothers,two in prison.
帮个小忙?  没问题
Accept a call? Yes.
不过帮他们逃出来?  太疯狂了
But break them out? Loco.
我的哥哥给了我一个棒球手套
My brother gave me a baseball mitt
作为14岁的生日礼物
for my 14th birthday.
所以 我欠他的
I owed him.
你这个作兄弟的比我好啊
You're a better man than I am.
让时间来见证吧
Time will tell.
他们到现在应该打电话来了吧
Shouldn't they have called by now...about the plane?
是的
Yeah.
但是  我有个问题
You know, I...I have a question.
我想
I thought
我觉得这些应该是玻璃管装
that these came in glass vials,
不是塑料装的
not plastic.
我也怀疑过 但是卖我的人说
I thought so, too, but the guy I bought it from said
就是用塑料管包装的
he packed it in plastic
再运输过程中防碎 防火
for transportation over long distances to prevent a fire
或者防爆炸
or an explosion.
真的?
Really?
怎么从来没有听过
I never heard of that.
怎么了
我们要做一些品质鉴定
We're going to do a little quality control test.
这是最好的现货
It's the best available.
我们不急
We got time.
上次 一些二十出头的黑人
For the last time,some black male, early 20s,
从我后面跳了出来
jumped me from behind.
我连他们的脸都没看清楚
I didn't get a good look at his face.
凶手从背后袭击的你？
The assailant attacked you from behind?
就是这样
That's what I just said.
他试图攻击你的前额
Yet he managed to make contact square on your forehead.
对啊
That's right.
用什么敲的?回旋镖?
With what? A boomerang?
别这样 告诉我到底发生了什么了
Come on, why don't you tell me what happened?
听着 我是一个退休的伊利诺斯州狱警
Look, I'm a retired correctional officer out of Illinois.
要不要展示下我的专业礼仪？ 宝贝
How about showing some professional courtesy, honey?
我是罗伊 格雷  请留言
This is Roy Geary.Leave a message.
你这个狗娘养的
You thieving son of a bitch.
最好跪下来
You better get down on your knees
向上帝祈祷别让我找到你
and pray to God that I don't find you,
如果你被我逮到
because, if I do,mark my words,
小心你的小命
I'm going to gut you bow to stern.
今天早上总统莱娜斯在佛罗里达州塔拉哈西市
President Reynolds was in Tallahassee, Florida,
参加了一个为正在重选的
early this morning, attending a $5,000-a-plate breakfast fund-raiser
参议员马丁 奎汉茨举行的筹款会
for senator martin kleinhenz,who's running for reelection.
今天下午  记者招待会被搅乱了
Later this afternoon, her press conference was derailed
一个记者要求评论
when a reporter asked her to comment
关于林肯逃狱的事情
on Lincoln Burrows'escape from custody.
她拒绝了
She declined.
这表明了在她上任一个月以来
It's become clear in her first month in office
都不能脱离和这次猎捕行动的关系
that she cannot separate herself from this manhunt.
只要猎捕行动还在进行
And as long as it continues...
...专家们分析关于布伦斯的问题会继...
...pundits say that questions about Burrows will contin...
女士们
Ladies.
让我们开始狂欢吧
Let's get this party started.
在过去30年中我恨你
The last 30 years,I've hated you.
你抛弃了我
You walked out on me.
你都没有见过迈克尔
You haven't even seen Michael.
我见过了
I've seen him before.
不是在报纸上 爸爸
Not in the papers, Dad.
我一直在想什么样的男人会放弃家人
Been trying to work out what kind of man abandons his family.
现在我在做同样的事情
Now I'm doing the same damn thing.
你会见到他的
You'll see him again.
我保证
I'll make sure of it.
还要开多久
How much further?
3小时
About three hours.
还有几分钟了
It's gonna be a few minutes.
我的兄弟就到这里了
My brother should be here soon.
可能我应该出去 确保他能够看见我
Maybe I should go outside and make sure he can see me.
好主意
That's a good idea.
我派伊内斯多去做
I think I'm gonna send Ernesto to do it.
(西班牙语)
Ernesto, por favor.
你好
Hello.
(西班牙语)
是不是有消息了?
Was that the call?
是的
Yes, it was.
关于飞机的?
About the plane?
(西班牙语)
糖水
Sugar water.
你犯了个大错误
You just made a big mistake,blanquito.
对不起 对不起 好吗?
I'm sorry, I'm sorry, okay?
我不是个化学家
I'm not a chemist.
卖给我的家伙发誓说是医用硝化甘油
The guy I bought it from swore it was medical nitro.
我们都被耍了
We both got screwed.
是的 但是只有一个人会付出代价
Yeah, but only one of us is gonna pay for it.
听着 我只想从这出去
Look, I just want to get out of here,
而你想得到你要的报酬
and you want your payment.
我的兄弟很快就来了
My brother's gonna be here soon.
我们可以商量
We'll work something out.
出个价吧
Just name your price.
我已经出价了
I already named my price.
但你没有兑现
You didn't go through.
你的兄弟到底什么时候到
When's your brother getting here?
你一直在盘算着利用我们  对不对
You were planning on turning us in the whole time, weren't you?
他什么时候能到
When's he supposed to meet you here?!
(西班牙语)
放下枪  否则我就开枪了
Drop it, or I'm gonna shoot him.
让他走  否则我就杀了你
Let him go, or I'll shoot you.
(西班牙语)
在哪?
Where is it?
我爸爸没给我任何东西
My father didn't give me anything.
你为了谁而拿自己的命冒险?
Who you risking your life for?
林肯 布伦斯吗?
Lincoln Burrows.
街头的暴徒而已
Street thug.
你为什么会那么想?
And why is that your concern?
我是说 这难道是医生立下的誓言吗
I mean, is there somewhere in the Hippocratic Oath
所谓的 我保证会冒着生命危险去救毫不关心我的人
where it says,"I pledge to risk my life for those who don't care about mine"?
他们是不会关心你的生死的
'Cause they don't care about yours.
布伦斯和迈克尔 斯科菲尔德是在利用你
Burrows and Michael Scofield just used you.
你是否感到很惊讶这个世界上还是有人会
Are you that surprised that there are people in the world
勇敢的抵抗像你这样的人?
who will stand up to people like you?
你连这都不知道吗?
Are you that far gone?
很可爱
That's cute.
真是悲哀啊
Sad.
但很可爱
But cute.
克里夫兰什么?
A Cleveland what?
别担心  我会慢慢跟你说的
Don't worry,I'll talk you through it.
我们这儿有张玻璃咖啡桌
And we got a glass coffee table right here.
才不干
Hell no.
给一千我就做
I'll do it for a thousand.
500$
1000$
750$
好吧
All right.
什么鬼东西?
What the hell?
闪人
Leave.
你知道
You know,
在军品店你能买到很多不可思议的东西
it's amazing what you can pick up at an Army-Navy store.
那些折磨你的手段都是贝利克的主意
All that torture stuff,that was Bellick's idea.
我也觉得他做的太过分了
And if you ask me, he took the whole thing way too far.
听着
Listen,
我分你一半钱  然后我们就此了解?
why don't I just give you half the money,and we call it a day?
好吧  六四开
All right, 60-40.
好吗 T 万事好商量
Come on, T,we can deal.
飞机会降落在哪儿?
Where's the plane going to land?
去死吧混蛋
Kiss my ass, cobarde.
我们该怎么做?
What are we going to do?
我也不知道
I don't know yet.
我们不能从地面穿越边境
We're not going to get across the border on the ground.
没飞机我们就完了
Without that plane,we're screwed.
他失血过多了
He's losing too much blood.
他这样活不下去的
He'll never make it like this.He should have thought
在他开枪打我们的时候就应该想明白的
of that before he tried to kill us.
我们必须要送他去医院
We got to take him to a hospital,
不然他会死的
or else he'll die.
求你了
Please.
告诉我飞机的事我就让你们走
The plane,and we'll let you go.
（西班牙语）
芬雷路...
Finley Road...
8号高速公路旁边有一个停机坪
off of Highway 8,there's an airstrip.
这样好了吧？快放了我们
There, okay?Now let us go.
-我们走吧!-别!别!不要!
-Let's go.-No, no, no!
迈克尔我们走
Michael, let's go.
求你了帮帮忙
Por favor... please.
迈克尔我们走
Michael, let's go.
别这样  求你了
Don't do this,please don't do this.
我们走吧迈克尔
Let's go, Michael.
如果换了我们在流血
If we were bleeding
他才不会在乎
he would have not lifted a finger,
你知道的  他会把我们俩都杀了
you know that--he was gonna kill us both.
-我们走吧-不  不会那样的
-Let's go.-No, that's not true.
迈克尔我们要去赶飞机了...
Michael, we're going to get to that plane...
别这样
Don't do this.
快走吧！
Let's go now, please.
求你别这样?!
Please don't do this, okay?!
（西班牙语） 别这样
Callate!Don't do this.
别这样好吗?
Don't do, all right?
别听他的!
Don't listen to him!
求你了
Please.
莎拉  我很在乎你的
Sara, I care about you.
这不是我情愿干的事  莎拉
This is not what I wanted, Sara.
克里曼
Kellerman.
莎拉那边情况怎么样了?
What's going on with Sara?
她和你交代什么了吗?
Has she told you anything?
哪儿也别去
Don't go anywhere.
还没
Not yet.
我想你是...用心劝导过她了
I trust you've been...persuasive.
是的当然
Yes, absolutely.
那就杀了她
Then kill her.
可她是知道点事情
Well, she knows something.
违背我的命令  你就完了
You disobey me, you are done.
明白了吗?
Do you understand me?
干掉她  保罗
Put her in the ground, Paul?
迈克尔
Michael.
我们走
Let's go.
-迈克尔-等等
-Michael.-Hold still.
迈克尔  这么做是个大错误  我们该快点离开
Michael, we're doing it wrong--let's get out of here.
现在他肯定会去报警
Now, he's gonna call the cops,
-或者去叫他的人来-他办不到的
or go get his buddies...He's not going to make it.
你必须要...别动！
You have to...Callate!
等安全了我们再打电话叫人帮他们
We'll call them when we get safe.
我们走  迈克尔  我们走!
Let's go-- Michael, let's go!
谢谢你
Thank you.
你们必须马上送他去医院
You got to get him to a hospital right away.
好的
Okay.
等下等下
Wait. Wait.
伙计...
Hey, man...
忘了芬雷路吧
Forget Finley Road.
飞机会停在7英里路标处
The plane is going to stop at the seven mile marker
在日落的时候  4号公路
on Route 4 at sunset.
会停五分钟
It's going to stop for five minutes.
然后它就会飞往
Then it's going to go
墨西哥的奥克萨卡
to Oaxaca, Mexico.
要是错过了你麻烦就大了
If you miss it,you're out of luck.
在来的路上流血过多死了
He bled out on the way over.
能确认身份吗?
Any ID?
知道  罗伊 盖瑞  是个外地人
Yeah, Roy Geary,just an out-of-stater.
你认识他?
You know him?
是我一个朋友
He's a friend of mine.
贝利克先生?
Mr. Bellick?
怎么
Yeah.
介意我再多问你几个问题吗?
You mind answering a few more questions?
是我
Yeah.
我是潘
It's Pam.
出什么事了?
What's going on?
只是想问个好
I just wanted to say hey.
你没事吧?
Well... are you all right?
你说是要紧事
You said it was important.
我知道事情一直往糟糕的方向发展...
I know things got kind of ugly toward the...
你知道的...一直到最后
you know, the end.
恩...糟糕的其实是我自己
Um... I got ugly.
不过我想让你明白  在某些情况下
But I want you to know that,that there were circumstances
恩...
that, uh...
也许对你和卡麦隆来说
It was better that you and Cameron
没和我在一起反而更好
that you were not with me.
为什么你现在跟我说这个?
Why are you telling me this now?
如果我有机会重头再来的话...
If I had to do it all over again...
我不会象当初那么做了
I'd do it different.
我们还会是一家人
We'd still be a family.
为此我愿意付出一切
I'd give anything for that.
我只想让你知道
I just wanted you to know.
亚力山大...
Alex...
出什么事了?
what's going on?
没事
Nothing.
我只想打电话给你跟你说....
I just wanted to call to say that I was, uh....
...我很抱歉
...that I'm sorry
对这一切
about everything.
你现在在哪儿?
Where are you right now?
我来找你
I can come get you.
那可真温馨  是吧?
Wouldn't that be nice, huh?
我是认真的  你在哪儿?
No, I'm serious.Where are you?
还有件事
One more thing.
如果你在媒体上听到什么...
If you hear anything in the media...
什么?
What?
你在说什么?
What are you talking about?
我爱你
I love you,
替我吻下卡麦隆好吗?
and give Cameron a kiss for me okay?
我很高兴当初跟你说了这地方
Well... I'm glad I told you about this place.
我也很高兴能搞懂怎么用GPS
I'm glad I figured out how to work a GPS.
下次能不能搞再复杂点?
Could you make it a little more difficult next time?
我欠你一次
I owe you one.
我们扯平了
We're even.
但现在我们要走了
But we got to leave.
林肯
Linc.
老兄
Hey, buddy.
你怎么样?
How are you doing?
-LJ在哪儿？-安全的地方
-Where's LJ?-Safe.
-那些钱呢？-慢慢再跟你说  我们要走了
-The money?-I'll tell you later;we got to go.
我带了个人过来
I brought someone.
爸爸?
Dad?
我们以前见过
We've met before.
你现在必须告诉我  好吗?
This is happening right now, okay?
别逼我这么做
Don't make me do this.
就算我知道也不告诉你
Even if I knew,I wouldn't tell you.
不告诉我?  是吗？
You wouldn't? Really?
你有那么笨?
Are you that stupid?
你居然那么愚蠢?!
Are you that stupid?!
因为你现在必须要死了!
Because now you're going to die!
你要死了 除非你告诉我
You're going to die,and all you had to do
你父亲给了你什么
is tell me what your father gave you.
我知道我的处境
I know my options.
要么什么也不说的死  或者说了
I can not tell you and die,or I can tell you
还是死
and still die.
错了
No. Wrong.
莎拉
Sara.
得了  放聪明点吧!
Come on, smarten up!
哪怕你一辈子就这么一次
For once in your life.
拜托了
去死吧
Go to hell.
溺死是很恐怖的   别误解我
Huh? Drowning is horrific--don't get me wrong--
但是一到你憋不住让水进到肺里
but once you give in and let the water come into your lungs,
会产生某种快感
there's a certain
我听说的
euphoria... I hear.
我猜作为一个瘾君子
I guess as a junkie,
我想你大概会喜欢那样
I thought maybe you'd appreciate that.
是你让自己落到这种下场的
You did this to yourself.